productusp.com 2011-05-25

# Privacy Policy | Product Reviews With Their Unique Selling Point

### Privacy Policy

ProductUSP.com is committed to present the latest technological advancements to all its visitors and is working towards presenting the best-in-class technology experience. There would be a few sections on our website that would require you to input a few of your personal details such as your full name, company and email address. However, all the information collected on this site shall remain with those who run the site and not shared with any other company or any other party. It would be advisable to all the users that they refer to this privacy policy.  
Information

All the visitors of this site are notified through this privacy policy that we shall never distribute, sell or barter any of their personal information to any third party on the cyberspace. Information collection would solely depend on the page you visit, for an example you wouldn’t be required to input any information while accessing the index page but at the time of leaving an opinion or a review or discuss on the forums, you would be required to provide some of your basic personal information. We do not hold any responsibility about the information required by the websites listed on www.productusp.com

We, as a company, monitor all the information that is exchanged through our site in order to avoid the inappropriate activities through our site. It would imperative for our users to know that there is some data which is collected automatically with the tools employed by us and one such example would be the IP address. It allows the site owners to know the physical location of the computer from where the specific content was posted. Such information is treated as being highly private and would not be shared to any unauthorized company except the government organisations with an official permission to do so.  
The products listed on the website are not manufactured by ProductUSP.com

Visitors are hereby informed that we merely provide a platform to understand and review these products in terms of usability and technology advancements. Hence we do not sell these products and hold no responsibility if you happen to buy these products based on the reviews published on our site.

This privacy policy is subject to change without notifying the visitors prior to the change. Hence it would be best for the users to have a check on this policy. Lastly, as a company we abide by all the rules and regulations when it comes to the information on our website in order to provide the best possible technology experience. By visiting ProductUSP.com, we assume that the users are in acceptance of this privacy policy.
